undergear.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy and Security | Undergear

We are here to answer your questions on our privacy policy:  
Undergear  
455 Park Plaza Drive  
La Crosse, WI 54601  
1-800-853-8555  

Where you go and what you do—What we know without you telling us!

Data about your activity while here on this site is automatically provided to Undergear® when you sign on. For example, we collect the e-mail addresses of visitors and customers who click on Undergear® marketing links or those who register online at Undergear® website; we collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, how many visits we get, and information such as where visitors arrived from as far as other sites on the Internet or if they directly typed our website address into their browser. E-mail addresses we collect are only used to transmit promotional e-mail offers to those customers and visitors who voluntarily agree to receive such promotional material from us or to send information about customer transactions. Your e-mail address will never be sold or shared for marketing purposes. 

Regardless of whether you sign on to our site, we also receive, store and analyze certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," (discussed below) and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our site such as the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call our toll free number. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

Cookies—How we know what we know without you telling us!

When you come to Undergear® or when you register with Undergear® we create your personal profile, assign a personal identification number, then send this personal identification number back to your computer's hard drive in the form of a "cookie," which is a very small bit of code. A "cookie" is very small text file placed on your hard drive by a Web Page server. It serves as your personal identification card, and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. The use of cookies is an industry standard; you will find them at most major Web sites. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you're at our site. We never save passwords or credit card information in cookies. 

Cookies enable us to know more about your use of the site, and allow you to utilize some of our website's functionality, and correspond with us about your personal profile without having to fill out registration forms with information you've already provided. We use cookies to record session information, such as items that you added to your shopping cart and to conduct marketing tests on our Web pages. By showing how and when you use the site, cookies help us see which areas and products are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with cookies. We use the information from cookies to provide services better tailored to our visitors' needs. The purpose of a "cookie" is to tell the server that you returned to that Web page. Of course, if you never register or leave personal information with Undergear® then the server only knows that someone with your cookie has returned to the Web site. You are in charge of deciding whether we know anything about you. But the more you tell us about yourself, the more we can help you find information or products you want.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the Undergear® website and its functionality and links will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, entering giveaways, or creating your personal profile. You can order your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered. Then you can decide whether to accept one or not. If you want to control which cookies your computer accepts, just follow the instructions for your particular Internet browser system located at <http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.mspx>

Your E-mail address—Do We Know It?

Your e-mail address and other personally identifying data about you is known to Undergear® only when you voluntarily submit it to Undergear® or if you click on one of our promotional e-mail marketing links. We may collect your e-mail address if you post a message to us, if you communicate with us via e-mail, if you ask us to communicate with you by e-mail such as for a confirmation of your order or shipment advice, or if you volunteer it for any reason, such as survey information and/or site registration, or sign-up for a Newsletter, and if you started but did not complete an order.

Your E-mail address—What Do We Do With It?

If you begin to place an order from this website, and if you have at any time given us your e-mail address, we may use your e-mail address to communicate with you about the status of your order. We may also send you e-mails regarding special sales, exclusive offers, and other valuable promotions that we think will interest you if you have voluntarily agreed to receive such promotional material.

If you enter one of our giveaways, Tel.e.Friend® about one of our products, or sign up for one of our Newsletters, and give us your e-mail address, we may use your e-mail address not only for the purpose it was submitted, but also to send you e-mails regarding our own special sales, exclusive offers, and other valuable promotions that we think may interest you if you have voluntarily agreed to receive such promotional material.

Like many other online merchants, we participate in cooperative database services which assist us in the matching of offline and online purchasing behavior, and marketing analysis, so that participants can better analyze and understand the differences and tendencies of print catalog purchasers and website visitors, and so that we can maximize the benefit of postal mail and e-mail we send to you. This sharing of information allows us and other interested parties to make future marketing efforts more efficient. These cooperative database services and their participants, however, are not authorized by Undergear® to use your e-mail address to send you e-mail.

If you would prefer not to receive emails from us regarding special sales and exclusive offers, [click here](http://www.undergear.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-undergear-Site/default/Page-Show?cig=default%2fAccount-Show).

Personal Information Other Than Your E-mail Address

Your California Privacy Rights Undergear® has a policy of not disclosing the personal information of our customers to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes if our customers have exercised their option to prevent that information from being disclosed to third parties for such purposes. The following paragraphs explain what we do with your personal information and how you can prevent it, or simply [click here]() to change your privacy preferences.

We use your shipping and payment address, and the address you give to us when you "register" your profile with us, to send you our print catalog and catalogs of our participating third-party merchants and affiliated companies which we feel will be of interest to you, all by postal mail.

If you have given us your telephone number, when registering your profile with us or when ordering merchandise from us, we may use your telephone number to reach out to you to follow up on your order of merchandise, including follow-up marketing. We do not share your telephone number with any outside parties for any purpose whatsoever.

We indefinitely maintain all of the information you give to us, to help us serve you better and to understand our customers and their purchasing patterns over time. Any payment information that is maintained by us is masked to keep it protected in the unlikely event of unauthorized breaches of security.

In addition, we may also share your name, address, e-mail address and purchase information directly with select merchants who are marketing affiliates of ours or other third parties. We use this information to match against our own offline catalog information (available from our records and other sources, such as demographic information and past purchase history) and we allow our marketing affiliates to use this information to match against their own offline information (available from their records and other sources, such as demographic information and past purchase history). This sharing of information allows us and other interested parties to make future marketing efforts more efficient. It may be used by our select marketing affiliates to send you offers of interest, by regular postal mail. If at any time we are required to share your full credit card information with marketing affiliates so they can bill you for a product or service, you will be made aware at the time of offer that the product or service is being provided directly by that vendor and we will clearly ask for your consent to make that transfer of your credit card information through secure transmission.

Like many other online merchants, we participate in cooperative database services which assist us in the matching of offline and online purchasing behavior so that participants can better analyze and understand the differences and tendencies of print catalog purchasers and website visitors and we can maximize the benefit of postal mail and e-mail we send to you if you have signed up with us to receive postal mail or e-mail. It may be used by other cooperative database participants to send you offers of interest, by postal mail. 

If you prefer that we do not include you in lists of information we share with others, [click here]().

Opt-Out of Future Catalogs

If you have requested a catalog from us, or have purchased from us at any time, we will send you one of our catalogs. If for any reason you no longer wish to receive catalogs from Undergear®, please contact Customer Service at 1(800)853-8555.

Correction of Your Personal Profile

You can always edit or correct any personal information you give Undergear® by writing to us at: [service@undergear.com](mailto:service@undergear.com "Opens An Email to Undergear Customer Service").

Shopping Analysis Provided by Third Party

Undergear® uses a number of third party data gathering and analysis services, which aggregate information into broad categories to help us provide you better products, services, and improved websites. We refer to them here as our "Data Compilers". Our Data Compilers are contractually bound to keep our visitors’ and customers’ data absolutely secure and confidential, and only to analyze the information they have access to by the software we license from them and return it back to Undergear®. They have no rights to use this information for any purpose, match it against any other information in their possession, nor transfer or disclose this information to anyone other than to Undergear®.

Customer Privacy During Tracking By Our Data Compilers

Our Data Compilers have adopted privacy guidelines set by the Federal Trade Commission. Undergear® relies on our Data Compilers and encourages you to learn more about our each of their Privacy Standards and any available opt-out choices by [Coremetrics](http://www.coremetrics.com/company/privacy.php "Link To Coremetrics Privacy Policy") and ([Atlas Solutions](http://www.atlassolutions.com/privacy.aspx "Link To Atlas Privacy Policy")).

Access by The Operator of Our Affiliates Program

As a visitor to the Undergear® site, you may have arrived here through a link on one of our affiliate sites. Our affiliates operate websites which they use to conduct a business or generate revenues, and Undergear® compensates its affiliates based upon any purchases made by an affiliate-linked visitor to Undergear® site. The operator of our affiliates program, Commission Junction, in providing its services to us, does not deal directly with our customers. A visitor who clicks on a Undergear® link located on an affiliate's website is redirected, invisibly, through the website of Commission Junction, where its technology automatically records the IP "address" of the browser used by the visitor, but that address does not permit identification of the individual using the browser. In addition, during such redirection, Commission Junction may place a "cookie" on the hard drive of the visitor's computer through his or her Web browser (See description of cookies above). Commission Junction does not have access to data that identifies or permits the identification of any of Undergear® customers or visitors. The operator of our affiliates program encourages you to learn more about its privacy standards by clicking here: <http://www.cj.com/privacy_web_user.html>

Access By the Operator of Our Security Monitor

As a visitor to Undergear® site, the operator of our security monitor, ScanAlert will have access to your activity here. This web site is tested and certified daily to pass the FBI/SANS Internet Security Test. ScanAlert's security auditing technology allows the HACKER SAFE logo to appear only when a web site's current security status meets the highest published government standards. The access which we allow to ScanAlert for its HACKER SAFE service help protect you from identity theft and credit card fraud. According to ScanAlert, "HACKER SAFE does not mean hacker proof. HACKER SAFE certification cannot and does not protect any of your data that may be shared with other servers that are not certified HACKER SAFE, such as credit card processing networks or offline data storage, nor does it protect you from other ways your data may be illegally obtained such as non-hacker "insider" access to it. For more information about the privacy policies of ScanAlert and HACKER SAFE, go to <http://www.mcafee.com/us/about/privacy.html>.

Access by Third Party Advertising Companies

From time to time, we may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. In the course of serving advertisements to this and other sites, these companies usually collect information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our ads. Any information that these third parties collect is completely anonymous, is in a non-personal aggregate format, and is shared for purposes of analysis and improvement of our site. For instance, they may keep track of how many of our ads you had seen before visiting our site. This is primarily accomplished through technology, including cookies and action tags (commonly referred to as Web Beacons or GIF tags), which we will place on various pages within our Web site. These third party advertising companies may, in turn, use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide ads about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about the practices of our third party advertising contractors, if any, and to know how to contact them to advise them of your choices about not having your information used further, please [click here]( "Link to Nothing").

Access By Other Corporate Entities

We share much of our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with our parent company Hanover Direct, Inc., and its subsidiaries and affiliated catalog and e-commerce companies and other third parties. To the extent that you are not already a customer of such entity, they will do nothing with the information and will treat it at least as protectively as we treat the information we have about you. If you are already a customer of such entity, they may use this information to serve your needs better with respect to their merchandising, promotion, and marketing. We reserve the right to sell our customer database in the event Undergear® is acquired, dissolved, declared insolvent, files for bankruptcy or undergoes some other corporate change for which Undergear® is materially affected. If you are a customer of another Hanover Direct catalog company and prefer that we do not include you in lists of information we share with one of our affiliated marketing companies which they may use for promotion or marketing, please [click here]( "Link to Nothing").

It is possible that Undergear® Hanover Direct, or its affiliated companies, or any combination, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that Undergear® would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide Undergear® shopping experience. You will receive notice of such event (to the extent it occurs) as provided in the paragraph below entitled "Notice"", and we will require that the new combined entity follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information.

Problems

If at any time you have a question or dispute concerning your visit here, your order transaction, or our compliance with this privacy policy, you may contact us at [service@undergear.com](mailto:service@undergear.com "Opens An Email to Undergear Customer Service"). Please provide your first and last name, order number, if any, and, if you have a question about our merchandise, item number(s), and we will get back to you promptly. If we are unable to resolve your complaint to your satisfaction, you may elect to proceed to submit your complaint to an independent arbitrator to obtain an impartial assessment of your case, in writing. Any such arbitration will be deemed "conditionally binding", meaning that the decision of the arbitrator will be binding upon Undergear® if you elect to accept the decision, and it will be binding upon you as well. If your dispute concerns our compliance with this privacy policy, and if we are unable to resolve your complaint to your satisfaction, you may elect to proceed with BBB OnLine"s Privacy Policy Review Service by completing the [BBBOnline complaint form](http://www.bbbonline.org/about/privacy.asp "Link to the Better Business Bureau On-Line Complaint Form").

To Residents of a European Union Member Country (EU Residents)—Re: The DMA Safe Harbor Program

Brawn, LLC complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. [Your organization’s name] has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Brawn, LLC’s certification, please visit [www.export.gov/safeharbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/)

If you are an EU Resident, in the event you are not satisfied with the resolution by Undergear® of any questions or complaints you may have regarding your personal data in our possession, then you may submit your questions and complaints to the Direct Marketing Association ("DMA") Safe Harbor Enforcement Program as follows: e-mail: [safeharbor@the-dma.org](mailto:safeharbor@the-dma.org "Link Opens An Email To Safe Harbor"); mail: Safe Harbor Line, Direct Marketing Association, 1615 L Street, NW, Suite 1100, Washington, DC 20036, USA, Telecopier: 202-955-0085; Telephone: 202-861-2445.

### SECURITY

Security Policy

The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our customers and visitors is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Undergear® cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When your credit card information is transmitted to Undergear® we use industry standard, 3.0 SSL (secure socket layer) encryption to ensure the security of your information.

Important update about SSL Technology

Web browsers (such as Internet Explorer, Firefox, and Safari) support SSL technology to encrypt, or encode, your personal information before it is sent over the Internet. SSL versions 1.0 and 2.0 found in older browsers have known security weaknesses which could compromise your data. To ensure you're getting the best protection available, thecompanystore.com only allows secure transactions with browsers using SSL version 3.0 or higher. We recommend upgrading to the latest version of your browser software and downloading security updates as they become available.

The following browsers do support SSL version 3.0, however, if you do not upgrade to the newest versions you may need to change your browser settings to utilize it:

  * Internet Explorer 5.5 or higher (PC)
  * Internet Explorer 5.0 or higher (Mac)
  * Netscape 2.0 (Domestic) or higher (PC/Mac)
  * Firefox 0.8 or higher (PC/Mac/Linux)
  * Mozilla 1.7 or higher (PC/Mac/Linux)
  * Camino 0.8 or higher (Mac)
  * Safari 1.0 or higher (Mac)
  * Opera 1.7 or higher (PC/Mac)
  * Omniweb 3.0 or higher (Mac)
  * Konqueror 2.0 or higher (Linux)

We also have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at Undergear®. Nothwithstanding the foregoing, due to the open nature of the internet, We do not guarantee the absence of theft, hacker activity, electronic or non-electronic tampering, or computer crime, and we hereby disclaim responsibility and liability for stolen information.

Disclaimer

The Privacy Policy expressed herein and these statements constitute the present policy of Undergear® as to which it will take reasonable measures to implement. Similarly this Privacy Policy is not intended to be "advertising" or "advertising claims." Rather it is intended to set forth our policy, including our practices and intentions about how we conduct our business.

Notice

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. All changes to this policy which we deem material and which affect your personal identifiable information, are effective only after we provide you with at least thirty (30) days' notice of the changes by posting the changes here in Terms & Conditions for Use of Site and sending an e-mail to users who have provided us their e-mail address for this purpose. We provide you with thirty (30) days' notice to give you the opportunity to notify us if you do not agree to the changes we highlight to you in our e-mail notice. Our e-mails will normally remind you that you have the opportunity to inform us of your preferences, and will alert you how to inform us of your preferences by such e-mails and through this Privacy Policy. If we make any changes which have no effect upon the collection of your personal information (i.e., revisions to our access and access of third parties to your activities here on an anonymous basis only), then you will not receive an e-mail notification of the change. Such changes will become effective five (5) days after we post the revision to our Privacy Policy on this site.
